cougarboard.com 2017-06-24

# Privacy Policy - CougarBoard

## Privacy Policy

### Personal Information

The only personal information we collect is what you voluntarily offer during signup, and some basic information related to payments made on the site. We also store certain information we receive related to your use of the site, such as your IP address. Credit card numbers are never received nor stored, as all processing is handled by a third party. The personal information we do have will never be made available to others, with the following exceptions: (1) legal orders, such as subpoenas (2) repeated serious violation of site rules (3) appropriate requests from BYU compliance, licensing, legal, or other similar departments who need to contact CougarBoard users quickly and directly.

Also, moderators have access to some information to enable duplicate account checking. They also may have information that they have access to as part of the moderation of the site, such as abuse reports, appeals, and other information sent by users to the moderators. Moderators are not allowed to share any of that information with non-moderators or anyone not on this site, unless one of the above exceptions apply. 

### Social Networks

If you choose to connect your CougarBoard account to a social network account (such as Facebook, Twitter, etc), we will store basic information received from your social network account. This may include account ID, real name, email, and location, along with a list of those you have connected with on that network. If you choose to allow it, we will let your social network connections who are also on CougarBoard know your CougarBoard username. 

### Cookies

We store a few cookies on your computer, related to logging in and to gathering statistics on unique visitors. 

### Surveys

Information you provide in surveys will remain confidential. Survey data will only ever be published in aggregate form. 

### Message Board Posts, Boardmails, Chat, etc.

This site allows you to post messages in various formats, either to the public, to groups, or to individuals. All messages are owned by whoever posted them. By posting to CougarBoard.com, you agree to allow your message to be published on the Internet by CougarBoard.com.

Posts to the message board may be edited or deleted by the user until the post is put into the "archive", according to the board archive policy at the time. After that, posts may not be edited or deleted from our archive. Moderators may still have access to edited or deleted posts.

Boardmails, chat, and other message formats supported by this site do not allow editing or deletion, but have a limited audience. Please be aware of that when posting personal information. 

### Emails

Users who have signed up for CougarBoard may occasionally receive administrative emails. 

### Analytics

We collect web analytics information about our users in order to help us run the site more effectively. For example, web analytics allows us to see trending information about page views per day, or even things like what percentage of users are using each browser. Our web analytics are provided by third parties, and their privacy policies apply to the information they collect. 

### Third Party Advertising

CougarBoard.com is supported largely by advertising. We use various third party ad services to provide the ads that you see on the site. We cannot control what (if any) information is stored by these services. We do not provide any personal information about our users to these services. 

Our ad networks use cookies to serve ads on this site. For example, Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy. 

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>. 

## Future Changes

If our Privacy Policy changes at some time in the future we will post the policy changes to our Web site to notify you of these changes.
